Nishu Kawale

Gmail: nishukg04@gmail.com

Salesforce: https://trailblazer.me/id/shivakawale4 | GitHub: https://github.com/Nishucode |

Portfolio Website: https://nishucode.github.io/DesignDynamoPro/

PROJECTS

Analog Clock, Creator
Sticky Notes, Creator
Password Generator
Snake Game
Spotify Clone
Myntra Clone
World Clock with Alarm
Weather App
Password Manager
Number Guessing game
Question-Answer Quiz

Developed front-end user experience using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Visual Studio Code.

Implemented the **DOM** (Document Object Model) to manipulate the HTML and CSS of the applications.

Used python, Visual Studio Code, Windows PowerShell.

Custom App for Showroom to keep track of new Vehicles using Salesforce CRM

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Intern AICTE India 07-2022 to 11-2022

- Worked with various salesforce.com Standard objects like Accounts, Contacts, Leads, Cases, Campaigns, Reports and Dashboards.
- Worked on Email-to-Case functionality, sequencing of Cases and Visibility of the Emails to the front end of the portal.
- Used Force.com developer toolkit including Apex Classes, Apex Triggers and Visualforce pages to develop custom business logic.
- Written Apex classes, Controller classes, Apex Triggers for implementing Customer search and adding customers to salesforce standard Account object.
- Worked with SOQL and SOSL queries for manipulation of large data sets and performed DML operations using SOQL Statements and Database methods.
- Customized security controls, setting-up delegated administrator, password requirements, session-setting, network access, and profile-level-security measures to ensure data protection in Salesforce.

Research Assistant

CSCP Wuppertal Germany

09-2021 to 12-2021

- Worked on projects such as Resource & energy efficiency, European Green Deal, Sustainable Horticulture, MERLIN project, Marine environment & Coral reefs, and Sustainable Tourism, and supported training materials on various topics.
- Gained valuable experiences Circular economy, value chain green finance green banking, tender procedures in procurement of projects on Waste management green banking.

Research Assistant

Global 2030, Berlin Germany

11-2020 to 07-2021

- Worked on UN millennium Goals (MDGs) like Hunger, to eradicate & combat world problems targeted.
- Managed research updates for facts, figures, measures taken or recommended on topics covered by the UN Millennium Development Goals (MDG) in order to provide further direction for policymakers.

CERTIFICATION

Responsive Web Design, Free-code Camp

Salesforce Certified Associate Certification, SalesforceCredential ID: 260944801-10-2022Salesforce Certified Admin Professional Course, SimplilearnCredential ID: 351979206-2022Salesforce Admin & App Builder Course, SimplilearnCredential ID: 355833206-2022

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python Git, Visual Studio Code, Adobe Photoshop, Responsive Web Design Salesforce Administration, Salesforce.com Development, Salesforce Lightning Design System

EDUCATION

Masters in Urban Development B.Tech. in Urban Planning

Technische Universität Berlin, Germany College of Engineering Pune, India

Hindi: Proficient

10-2018 to 12-2020 07 -2013 to 07-2017

German: Intermediate

- Awarded for Guinness World Record-Largest floating design.
- Awarded with Katalyst Scholarship.
- Certified Remote Sensing, Geographic information system Urban Planner by ISRO.
- Contributed in **NOSPLAN** (National Organization of Students of Planning) in Informal Event-Extempore Competition as volunteer.

LANGUAGES

Marathi: Mother tongue • English: Proficient •